<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CATS Applicant Tracking System</title>
    <link>https://dk-cats.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CATS Applicant Tracking System</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 21:49:37 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dk-cats.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Strategy</title>
      <link>https://dk-cats.github.io/blog/social-media-sourcing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 21:49:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dk-cats.github.io/blog/social-media-sourcing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Strategy</title>
      <link>https://dk-cats.github.io/blog/social-media-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 21:49:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dk-cats.github.io/blog/social-media-strategy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://dk-cats.github.io/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 01:53:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dk-cats.github.io/resources/</guid>
      <description>Chrome Extension The CATS Chrome Extension automates parsing of candidate data from popular websites and social networks like LinkedIn, Monster, and CareerBuilder.
Download Now
Firefox Add-On The CATS Firefox Add-on automates parsing of candidate data from popular websites and social networks like LinkedIn, Monster, and CareerBuilder.
Download Now
WordPress Plugin This plugin is used to pull your job listings from the CATS Applicant Tracking System and display them on your WordPress site by using a shortcode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Cats</title>
      <link>https://dk-cats.github.io/why-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 01:52:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dk-cats.github.io/why-cats/</guid>
      <description>CATS helps thousands of companies from all over the world fill their hiring needs. From one person recruitment shops to the Fortune 500 operations, our customers rely on us to help them grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Cases</title>
      <link>https://dk-cats.github.io/use-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 01:51:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dk-cats.github.io/use-cases/</guid>
      <description>Currently, nearly 6,000 professional recruiters in 70 countries use CATS to solve their hiring challenges. CATS customers include small and large executive search firms, staffing agencies, technology startups, non-profits, Fortune 500 companies — anyone who needs to manage the hiring process in a professional and efficient manner.
Play Video Master Technology Group logo Master Technology Group Installation Company
Eden Prairie, MN Everything is all-in-one in the CATS system. When I have an open position, I can create it very easily, very quickly in CATS, and with one click of the button it sends it to every job board that I use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Features and Benefits</title>
      <link>https://dk-cats.github.io/features-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 01:51:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dk-cats.github.io/features-benefits/</guid>
      <description>The Applicant Tracking System that started it all For professional recruiters The ultimate tool for professional recruiters, CATS Pro has everything you need to be a top performer in the competitive world of talent acquisition. Build your custom hiring process using our industry-leading workflow system.
Manage The heart of recruitment is your client relationships. Our CRM was designed with professional recruiting in mind.
Engage​ All of our communication tools plus mass emailing and multiple industry leading email marketing integrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing</title>
      <link>https://dk-cats.github.io/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 01:50:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dk-cats.github.io/pricing/</guid>
      <description>Get Started Includes a customizable careers page (or embeddable jobs widget for your website) and our industry-leading workflow to supercharge your hiring process.
Annually / Monthly
$99 / $69
per user
Start Free Trial Included Features:
Meeting Scheduler
SMS Texting (US &amp;amp; Canada)
2- way Calendar &amp;amp; Email sync
Recruiting browser extension
Custom access levels
Sponsored Job Posting
$1000 $500 data migration</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Processing Policy</title>
      <link>https://dk-cats.github.io/data-processing-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 03:01:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dk-cats.github.io/data-processing-policy/</guid>
      <description>The processing of Personal Data in a secure and transparent way is important to us at CATS. Because of this, we are committed to processing Personal Data in accordance with the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”).
This Data Processing Addendum (“DPA”) amends the Terms of Service agreement between CATS Software, Inc (“CATS”) and you as a customer.
Definitions  “Controller” means the natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of personal data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>https://dk-cats.github.io/terms-of-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 03:01:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dk-cats.github.io/terms-of-service/</guid>
      <description>By using the catsone.com web site (“Service”), a service of CATS Software, Inc., you are agreeing to be bound by the following terms and conditions (“Terms of Service”).
CATS Software Inc. reserves the right to update and change the Terms of Service from time to time without notice. Any new features that augment or enhance the current Service, including the release of new tools and resources, shall be subject to the Terms of Service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use</title>
      <link>https://dk-cats.github.io/terms-of-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 03:01:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dk-cats.github.io/terms-of-use/</guid>
      <description>These Terms of Use are effective as of November 29, 2011.
1. Rules of Engagement This website, www.catsone.com (the “Site”), is owned and operated by CATS Software, Inc. (referred to as “CATS Software” “we,” “us” or “our”). PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE. By using this Site you agree to these terms of use (the “Terms”). If you do not agree to the Terms, please do not use the Site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://dk-cats.github.io/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 02:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dk-cats.github.io/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Last modified February 13, 2020
ATTENTION: PLEASE READ CAREFULLY THIS CATS Software SOFTWARE, INC. (“WE” OR “CATS Software”) PRIVACY POLICY (“PRIVACY POLICY”), WHICH IS PART OF THE CATS Software TERMS OF SERVICE (COLLECTIVELY “TERMS OF USE”), BEFORE YOU ACCESS, DOWNLOAD, OR OTHERWISE USE THEwww.catsone.com WEBSITE; OUR PRODUCTS AND SERVICES; OTHER INTERACTIONS (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ONLINE, OFFLINE AND BY PHONE OR MAIL) BETWEEN YOU AND US; AND/OR OUR SOCIAL MEDIA ACCOUNTS INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ALL CONTENT AVAILABLE THROUGH THESE PLATFORMS (COLLECTIVELY, THE “SERVICE”).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>